womenspost.ca 2008-03-15

# Women's Post: Privacy Policy

Women’s Post Privacy Policy (as of November 14, 2007)

We at Women’s Post highly value your privacy and we work hard to earn and keep your trust. In order to maintain your privacy, we strictly follow certain overall policies. We will never sell or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes, we will never share your contact information with another user, without your consent, and any sensitive information that you provide will be secured to the best of our capabilities. 

Notice of all changes that materially affect ways in which your personally identifiable data may be used or shared will be posted in updates to our Privacy Policy. If you continue to use any of the Women’s Post services after notice of changes have been published on our website, you hereby provide your consent to the changed practices.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you can view our help page at <http://www.womensportal.ca/help>. If you cannot resolve your issue via our help page, you should contact Women’s Post by email at [privacy@womenspost.ca](mailto:privacy@womenspost.ca).

Information We Collect

In order to become a Women’s Post user, you must first create an account. In the process of creating an account you must provide us with certain personal information, including your name, your email address and a password. We ask for other information to fill out your profile; however, this additional information is not required to open an account.

Like most web sites, Women’s Post uses cookies and web log files to track site usage. For more information on cookies, please visit <http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie>.

As per the communications standards on the Internet, we at Women’s Post use Apache web server logs and Google Analytics to track user data. This information is used to analyze overall trends to help us improve Women’s Post services. 

Children are not eligible to have a Women’s Post account and we ask that those under the age of 18 do not submit any personal information to us or use our services. If you believe that we have any information about or from anyone under the age of 18, please contact us at [privacy@womenspost.ca](mailto:privacy@womenspost.ca).

Uses of Information

Women’s Post services are designed to help professional women more effectively connect with other professionals. The personally identifiable information you choose to provide on our site is used to help you describe yourself to other users. Other information, that does not personally identify you as an individual, is collected by Women’s Post from the site (such as, by way of example, patterns of utilization) and is exclusively owned by Women’s Post. This information can be utilized by Women’s Post in such manner as Women’s Post, in its sole discretion, deems appropriate.

Women’s Post will communicate with you through email and notices posted on this website. These include a series of welcome emails which help inform new users about various features of the service. Please be aware that you will always receive certain emails from Women’s Post related to the proper functioning of your account, such as email notices when another wants to get in touch with you. Women’s Post may send you promotional information unless you have opted out of receiving such information. If you wish to opt-out of receiving promotional emails, please send a request to [customerservice@womenspost.ca](mailto:customerservice@womenspost.ca).

Sharing of Information

Women’s Post takes the privacy of our users very seriously. We will never sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to any third parties for marketing purposes.

Women’s Post offers a “public profile” feature which allows users to publish portions of their Women’s Post profile, including your name, but not your email address to the public Internet. Users may opt-out of providing all information except their name; however Women’s Post does not warrant how third-party search engines will update their cache.

We may provide aggregated data about the usage of our services to third-parties for such purposes as we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate. We may segment our users by such means as occupation, industry, location, company. If you would like to be excluded from the aggregated research or products based upon aggregated data about our users’ activities on the site, please email customer service.

It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on our company or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

Links to Other Websites

Women’s Post web pages may contain links to other websites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Women’s Post. 

Accessing and Changing Your Information

You can review the personal information you provided us and make any desired changes to the information, or to the settings for your Women’s Post account, at any time by logging in to your account on the Women’s Post website and editing the information on your Profile page. You can also close your account through the Women’s Post website. If you close your Women’s Post account, we will remove your name and other personally identifiable information from our publicly viewable data. We may retain certain data contributed by you if it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally-identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. All retained data will continue to be subject to the terms of the Women’s Post Privacy Policy that you have previously agreed to. To request that we close your account and remove your information from the Women’s Post website, please fill out and send the request form at <http://www.womensportal.ca/help/help>. You will receive a response to requests within five business days of our receiving it.

Security

In order to secure your personal information, access to your data on the Women’s Post website is password-protected. To protect any data you store on our servers we also regularly audit our system for possible vulnerabilities and attacks.

Contact Us

If you have questions or comments about this privacy policy, please email us at [customerservice@womenspost.ca](mailto:customerservice@womenspost.ca) or contact us by mail at: Women’s Post, 2 Carlton St., Suite 804, Toronto, ON, M5B 1J3.
